Getting to the root of the problem is like pulling teeth.
Novocaine is a comedy, crime, thriller film directed by David Atkins.
A dentist finds himself a murder suspect after a sexy
patient seduces him into prescribing her drugs.
Frank Sangster, played by Steve Martin.
Susan, played by Helena Bonham Carter.
Jean Noble, played by Laura Dern.
Pat, played by Lynne Thigpen.
Mike, played by Chelcie Ross.
Sally, played by Polly Noonan.
Novocaine is a 2001 American black comedy thriller film written and directed by David Atkins and
starring Steve Martin, Helena Bonham Carter, Laura Dern, Lynne Thigpen, and Elias Koteas.
It was shot in the Chicago, Illinois area.
The film premiered at the 2001 Toronto International Film Festival and went on to
screen in limited release in the United States on November 16, 2001.
It was a box-office bomb and received mixed-to-negative critic reviews.
The film explores themes of murder, drugs, dentist.
The tone is lighthearted and intense.